Haryanto S.T., M.Sc.

Software Engineer



Contact

â	1	No. 84, Gongzhuan Rd, Taishan District,
		New Taipei City, Taiwan, 243
\bowtie		Haryanto462@gmail.com
(Anto112.github.io
in		www.linkedin.com/in/haryanto-b05334ab
		https://github.com/anto112
6 9		+886 973 448 264

My name is haryanto, and I was born on February 12, 1996, in Tanjung Harapan, Indonesia. Experienced software engineer with a master's degree in image processing software development from the faculty of electronic engineering. Working under duress is not a problem for me, and I can communicate and interact effectively in a teamwork environment. I have a strong desire to learn about new technologies in order to keep up with it.

Education

2013 -2018

University of Bengkulu

Bachelor's degree - Mechanical Engineering

2019

2020

Ming Chi University of Technology

Master's degree - Electronic engineering

Language

Indonesian Native speaker

English Fluent

Capabilities and skills

Professional	Personal
Project plan	Leadership
Task management	Critical thinking
Teamwork/ collaboration	Adaptability
Problem solving	Self-control
Good communication	Optimism

Technical skills

O.C.	M W 1 M F 1
Office	Ms. Word, Ms. Excel,
	Ms. PowerPoint
Programing language	Python, C++, Matlab
IDE development	VS Code, PyCharm,
	google colabs, Jupyter
	notebook, Docker
Version control	Git, GitHub, GitLab
Wrapper tools	Ctypes, Pybind11
Operating system	Linux, Raspy OS,
	Windows
User interface app	PyQt, Tkinter (desktop
design	app)
	HTML, Markdown, CSS
	(Web Based)
Software 3D design	Tinker CAD, Inventor,
	Fusion 360
AI Framework	CNN, Mask R-CNN,
	YOLO
Digital Image	OpenCV, Moildev SDK,
Processing	Camera calibration,
	Fisheye image

Processing, Image

recognition, and related

Achievement

Global Project Based Learning

"Campus delegation to learning about software programing based on IoT (internet of Things)" Dong A University - 2020/Vietnam

Transcultural Humanities Summer Camp

"Participants in transcultural humanities activities to introduce culture in Taiwan"

Tzu Chi University of Science and Technology
- 2019/Taiwan

First price Teaching assistant

"Get the first price from teaching assistance competition held by the college of engineering, MCUT"

Ming Chi University of Technology - 2019/Taiwan

Project Internship from TEEP@Asia plus

"Awarded project internship from teep@asia plus during 3 moths in MCUT"

Ming Chi University of Technology 2018/Taiwan

Work Experience

Feb 2021 - Now	Ming Chi University of Technology Research Engineer
Sept 2018 - Dec 2018	PT. PAC Engineering Technical support
Sept 2018 - Dec 2018	PT. Bukit Asam Tbk (PTBA) Student internship

Project Experience

	Classification image Apps using deep
2022	"Develop apps to training multiple class of
	image for image classification using CNN"
2024	Monocular Visual Simultaneous
2021	localization and mapping (SLAM) using
Now	
TNOW	fisheye lens
2021	MOIL Apps: a sophisticated fisheye
	image processing application
2021	MOIL API: simplify the development
2021	plugin applications for MOIL Apps
2021	Monocular Visual odometry Using
2021	Multiple View from single fisheye image
2021	Develop apps for control intel T-265
2021	camera to create visual odometry dataset
	Colonoscopy Apps: Create a better
	perspective on the colonoscopy image
2020	and close to the common human visual
	perception.
2020	Lumen detection using Mask R-CNN
2020	Create module for streaming camera using
2020	raspberry pi that can access through internet
	Portable Learning Environment (PLE)
2020	Using Docker and Jupyter Notebook for
	Teaching a Programming Course
	Classroom management system: provide
	virtual machine (VM) for more than 40
2020	students in class for teaching the Linux
	operating system OS using Docker
	Build wrapper Moildev SDK to python:
	Moildev SDK was originally build by
2019	C++ to take the advantage of speed
	computation.
	Design of prototype control system of 4-
	dof (degree of freedom) manipulator
2018	
	arm robot as object transfer based on
	color using visual sensors

Organization experience

2020	Vice president Indonesian Student
2021	Association in Taiwan (ISA-Taiwan)
	Delegate of ISA-Taiwan at 13 th
2021	OISAA's International Symposium
	2021
2019	Vice chairman of Indonesia student
-	association in Ming Chi University of
2020	Technology
2015	Member of Assistant Design and
2015	Construction Laboratory in
2018	Mechanical Engineering, Bengkulu
2016	University
	Chairman of the Basic
2017	Education (basic orientation)
2017	Committee of Perkumpulan
	Konservasi Alam Teknik (Pulkanik)
	Temu Wicara dan Kenal Medan
2016	(TWKM) held by <i>Pencinta Alam</i>
2010	Students Indonesian Moslem
	University (MAPALA UMI), Makasar
	•

Training And Seminar

	One of Instructure at AI workshop
2022	between MCUT and UNAND
	using online platform
	Presented paper on the 4th
	International Conference on E-
	Society, E-Education, and E-
2020	Technology (ICSET 2020) with
2020	title "Portable Learning
	Environment (PLE)Using Docker
	and Jupyter notebook for Teaching
	a Programming Course"

	National Advocacy and
2016	Environment Training held by
2016	Mahasiswa Hukum Pecinta Alam
	(Mahupala)University of Bengkulu
	National Seminar with Ricky Elson
	and Paris El Hakim with the theme
2016	of Innovating for Independent
2016	Technology held by Mechanical
	engineering Student Association,
	Bengkulu University
	Development of Conservation
2045	Cadres and Nature Lovers Groups
2015	by Badan Konservasi Sumber Daya
	Alam (BKSDA), Bengkulu

Interest

